cleverstat.com 2009-03-18

# CleverStat Privacy Policy, Copyright Notice

### CleverStat

#### Privacy Policy, Copyright Notice

Privacy Policy

  * CleverStat shall never sell, rent or share any private information (such as e-mail addresses, names, postal addresses or phone numbers) received from you. 
  * CleverStat does not use any hidden methods to collect your personal information. We do not collect any information unless you explicitly provide it to us. The information acquired in such a way is used for sending newsletters to our customers, providing feedback or registering our software. 
  * This site (www.CleverStat.com) collects the following information about each visitor: visited pages, date and time, IP address, browser type and a referrer record indicating the website where you come from. This information is used for statistical purposes. 
  * This site (www.CleverStat.com) uses cookies technology to identify a visitor if he/she returns to our site. No personal information is collected except the one specified above. 
  * This site may contain links to other sites. CleverStat is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of these websites. 

Copyright Notice

This entire website and any software that available for downloading from this site is protected by copyright law and international copyright treaties. The use of this software shall be governed by the terms of the end user license agreements, if any, which come together or are included with the software ("License Agreement"). This software is made available for downloading solely for use by end users according to this License Agreement. Unless provided otherwise, the copying or reproduction of any material from this site to any other location for further reproduction or redistribution is expressly prohibited. Any reproduction or redistribution of the files that does not agree with the terms of the License Agreement is a violation of copyright law. 

All brand names appearing on this site are trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners.
